目指し歩いた夜空の向こうでは
ただ一羽のカラスが
急かすように叫んだ
遠く昔の記憶ではただの
ドクロの影が笑った
顔見てそう笑った
Oh ohohoh
So I just bleed and feel the blood I have inside me
Holding to the creed and blade to slay thee
Carry on the oath until my last scene
Higher than the sky and deeper than the sea
Keep your precious justice to yourself bud
Use it till they’re torn become a pile of mud
I don’t need their choice or voice to judge me
The one and only way I had and always seek
Anyone everyone I will crush ’em all
Enemies Let ’em see Now I see you fall
Kings and gods, Change the odds
I’m the one who makes my final call
傷も過去も孤独さえも
握り潰しただ争う
Keep your crown, I’ll take you down
I’m the one who makes my final call
Feeling like I’m almost there, but I’m not
音もない風に漂う bones
途切れて消えない声の方
何も知らないまま戻れないでしょう
同じ色の目にうつる
違う色の息を吐く
You’re gonna make me go
You’re gonna make me drown
失うものはもう何もない
You’re gonna make me go
You’re gonna make me drown
No, I don’t want it
I don’t want it
Don’t let me go
You’re gonna make me drown
Don’t let me drown
足場もない答え　前へ向かう
You’re gonna make me go
You’re gonna make me drown
No, I don’t want it
I don’t want it
But I know no one’s there
I will stay right here
はざまを辿って